Railway Labor Executives' Association Additional Records 5552
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, Legislative Council, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO Executive Council Bulletin, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, Executive Council, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  Reports
- Other Organizations. Misc. Organizations General, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  Includes Congressional Secretaries Club Gala Ad Book honoring Richard Nixon.
- Other Organizations. National Safety Council, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Other Organizations. U.S. Committee for the United Nations (Also General UN), 1970 (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Other Organizations. Transportation Research Forums, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Other Organizations. Charities - General, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Other Organizations. National Association of Retired and Veteran Railway Employees., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Other Organizations. Labor Bureau of Middle West, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Other Organizations. Labor Newspaper, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Financial statements.
- Other Organizations. Special Election Year Editions of Labor Newspaper, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  Includes editions of Labor newspaper.
- Other Organizations. National Association of Railroad Passengers (NARP), 1970 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  Includes pamphlet " Modern Trains for a More Mobile America."
- Other Organizations. Golden Spike, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Other Organizations. Conference of Transportation Trades, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  Includes minutes of executive committee meeting.
- International Affairs. International Affairs, General, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  Promotional pamphlets from the Iranian State Railway.
- International Affairs. Office of International Labor Affairs, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  Includes information on visits of foreign railroaders.
- International Affairs. International Affairs Team Managers, Office of International Labor Affairs, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- International Affairs. International Transport Workers Federation (ITF), 1970 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Commuter Problems. General, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Commuter Problems. Passenger Service Investigation, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Commuter Problems. Philadelphia Service Improvement Corp., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Commuter Problems. New Haven Problems Including New York Area (Long Island) (Staten Island), 1970 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Commuter Problems. Bay Area Rapid Transit (BART), 1970 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Commuter Problems. Port Authority Trans Hudson (PATH), 1970 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Commuter Problems. Adequacies, General, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Commuter Problems. Adequacies, Passenger Service of Southern Pacific between California and Louisiana, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  Docket # 34733. Case will be removed from the docket. ICC decided in favor of discontinuance.
- Commuter Problems. Adequacies, Passenger Service Between San Francisco and Chicago, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  Docket # 34924. Case will be removed from the docket. No further action by RLEA.
- Commuter Problems. Adequacies, Penn Central Elimination of Baggage Checking, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Commuter Problems. Commuter Service Improvements, HUD, Mass Transit Grants, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  Contains New York Times article about New York and Connecticut taking over the New Haven Railroad, forming MetroNorth Commuter Rail.
- Commuter Problems. Sec. 13(c) Agreement, Massachusetts Bay Transit Authority (MBTA), 1970 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  Boston and Maine Railroad entering into agreement with the MBTA.
- Commuter Problems. Sec. 13(c) Agreement - Chicago Transit Authority (CTA), 1970 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Commuter Problems. Southern Pennsylvania Transportation Project - Hatboro-Warminster, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  SEPTA
- Commuter Problems. Lake Porter County, Crown Point, Indiana, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  Application for a Capital Grant from the Urban Mass Transportation Administration
- Commuter Problems. Washington Metro Area Transit Authority, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- RLEA. 1971 File Guide (Box 19, Folder 30a)
- Government. Constitution, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 30b)
  Contains proposed amendments to Railroad Retirement Act.
- Government. Executive Branch, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Government. House and Senate, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Government. Government Agencies (General), 1971 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Government. Department of Transportation, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  Includes "Transportation Regulatory Modernization Act of 1971"
- Government. Transportation Association of America, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Government. DOT Studies, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Government. Federal Railroad Administration, Staff Appointments, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Government. Federal Railroad Administration, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  Includes pamphlet with information on accidents in 1969-1970
- Government. Office of High Speed Ground Transportation, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Government. Studies and Reports, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  Includes information on high-speed trains.
- Government. Bureau of Railroad Safety, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  Contains accident reports and statistics.
- Government. Railroad Safety Task Force, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  Includes reports on Track Maintenance and Safety Standards
- Government. Safety - Rules, Regulations, Petitions (FRA-DOTS), 1971 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Government. Highway Grade Crossing Matters, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  Includes report to Congress on highway safety.
- Government. Power Brakes, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 45)
- Government. Locomotive Inspection, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  Includes a special study on the footboards of diesel locomotives.
- Government. DOT, Rules, Standards and Instructions Cases in re Signals, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  Includes public notices and pamphlet "Rules, Standards, and Instructions for Railroad Signal Systems"
- Government. Approval of Changes in Signal Installation (BS-AP Cases), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Public notices
- Government. Hours of Service, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Government. Track Maintenance and Inspection Standards [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 20, Folder 4a)
  Includes pamphlet of proposed track safety standards.
- Government. Track Maintenance and Inspection Standards [folder 2 of 2], 1971 (Box 20, Folder 4b)
- Government. Equipment Safety Standards (Rolling Stock), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Government. Accidents Reports and Governing Regulations, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Government. Labor Department - General, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Government. Bureau of Labor Statistics [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 20, Folder 8a)
  Includes report "Technology and Manpower in the Railroad Industry in the 1970s"
- Government. Bureau of Labor Statistics [folder 2 of 2], 1971 (Box 20, Folder 8b)
- Government. Interstate Commerce Commission - General, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Government. ICC Membership and Staff Appointments, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Government. ICC Rules of Practice and Administrative Procedure, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Government. ICC Statistics, M-300, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Government. Statistics 240 Motive Power and Car Equipment, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Government. Statistics 200 Operating Statistics of Large Steam Railways, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Government. Statistics 125 Selected Income and Balance Sheets, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Government. Statistics 300-350 Steam Railways - Class I Wages, Monthly, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Government. Statistics 210 Train and Yard Service, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Government. ICC Ex Parte 278 - Equal Opportunity in Surface Transportation [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 20, Folder 18a)
  A suit brought before the ICC in re institutional racism and discrimination against people of color in federally regulated transportation industries. Included in this folder are initial filing by the plaintiffs and correspondence between RLEA executives.
- Government. ICC Ex Parte 278 - Equal Opportunity in Surface Transportation [folder 2 of 2], 1971 (Box 20, Folder 18b)
  Included in this folder is the initial filing by the EEOC claiming that the ICC has no jurisdiction in this matter, and that the case should be hear by that agency. Also included is the response from the ICC and initial filings from other parties.
- Government. ICC Ex Parte 278 - Equal Opportunity in Surface Transportation, File # 2 [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 20, Folder 19a)
  Includes initial filing by the NAACP and motions by involved parties.
- Government. ICC Ex Parte 278 - Equal Opportunity in Surface Transportation, File # 2 [folder 2 of 2], 1971 (Box 20, Folder 19b)
  Includes are initial statements and a motion to sever by the RLEA.
- Government. Motor Carriers - General, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  Contains pamphlet ":Freight Commodity Statistics."
- Government. National Mediation Board - General, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  Includes the annual report of the NMB.
- Government. National Mediation Board, Emergency Board Reports, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  Reports of Emergency Boards 178 and 179.
- Government. National Mediation Board Public Law Board Decisions on Procedural Questions, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Organizations Qualified to Participate in Selection of Members, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Membership and Staff Appointments, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Rules of Procedure and Administration, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Decisions and Certifications, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Second Division, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Third Division, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Fourth Division, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board - General, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Membership, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Application of Awards, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Third Party Notices, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board - General [folder 1 of 3], 1971 (Box 21, Folder 14a)
  Includes Quarterly Reports for the third quarter and a pamphlet containing tax tables for calendar year 1972.
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board - General [folder 2 of 3], 1971 (Box 21, Folder 14b)
  Includes quarterly report for the first quarter.
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board - General [folder 3 of 3], 1971 (Box 21, Folder 14c)
  Includes quarterly report for the fourth quarter.
- Government. Reports for RLEA Meeting from Railroad Retirement Board [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 21, Folder 15a)
  Includes financial statements, actuarial tables, and reports from the labor member of the Railroad Retirement Board, Neil Speirs.
- Government. Reports for RLEA Meeting from Railroad Retirement Board [folder 2 of 2], 1971 (Box 21, Folder 15b)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Membership and Staff Appointments, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Field Offices, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Status of Funds - Actuarial Reports, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Benefits and Railroad Unemployment Insurance Systems, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  Includes monthly benefit reports and information on 1971 amendments to the Railroad Retirement Act.
- Government. Railroad Retirement Annuities Affect. By P.L. 91-588 (Veterans' Pensions), 1971 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  Correspondence in re the cutting of retirement benefits to those drawing veterans' benefits.
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Educational Program, Meetings, Films, Etc., 1971 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Supplemental Retirement Plans (Supplemental Pensions), 1971 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Safety Studies, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, National Reporting Officers Memoranda, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Government. Administration of Medicare, Financial Intermediary, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Government. Commission on Railroad Retirement, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  Information on the newly formed Commission, and the concern that no representatives from the 15 labor unions that comprise the RLEA have been invited to attend or participate.
- Government. President's Committee on the Physically Handicapped [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 21, Folder 27a)
  Includes minutes of the annual meeting and pamphlets produced by the Committee
- Government. President's Committee on the Physically Handicapped [folder 2 of 2], 1971 (Box 21, Folder 27b)
- Government. National Railroad Passenger Corporation (Amtrak), 1971 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  Includes information on effects that Penn Central bankruptcy has on existing Agreements, lists of discontinued intercity routes, appointment of Charles Luna as the president of Amtrak, a list of station at which Amtrak trains will stop, job protection Agreements, and a report containing a map of the new Amtrak passenger services.
- Government. National Railroad Passenger Corporation (Amtrak), 1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  Includes Agreements between unions and Amtrak, train schedules for passenger service routes, pass privileges on Amtrak trains for employees, and employee protection Agreements.
- Government. National Railroad Passenger Corporation (Amtrak), File #2, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  Includes Agreements with railroad unions, information on employee train passes, opinions and awards of Referee Proceedings, legal filings by passenger advocacy groups, arbitration proceedings, and job protection agreements for employees.
- Government. National Railroad Passenger Corporation (Amtrak), File #2, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  Includes information on intercity train routes with maps, job protection Agreements, and a packet from a PR firm representing Amtrak.
- Government. President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Government. Civil Rights (Agenda Item 2:19) (formerly 3.66), 1971 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Government. Fast Freight Systems Transportation Corp., 1971 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  Includes legislation to create a government owned corporation to address national freight car shortage.
- Government. Economic Stabilization Pay Board, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  (Former File Title: Freedom from Hunger)
- Judicial. Court Cases - General, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  Includes information on dismissals of various civil rights cases
- Judicial. Union Shop Case (Street-Duckworth-Looper), 1971 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  With regard to the Penn Central bankruptcy reorganization.
- Judicial. Penn Central Bankruptcy, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  Includes lists of outstanding clams against Penn Central, a filing by the RLEA to intervene in the proceeding on behalf of its members, and authority of Penn Central trustees to transfer ownership of bridges to various states.
- Judicial. Boston and Maine Reorganization Case # 70-250, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Judicial. Louisville and Nashville Railroad - Union Shop Case, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Judicial. The Vanguard Association, Inc. of the Long Island Railroad, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Judicial. Seaboard Coast Line, Hamlet, N.C. (Civil Rights), 1971 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  Charges of discrimination filed against the carrier and various railroad labor unions.
- Judicial. Lehigh Valley Reorganization, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Judicial. Central Railroad Co. of New Jersey Reorganization: U.S.D.C. New Jersey No. B-401-67 [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1a)
  Includes statics on employees of CNJ, reports of tasks forces created to aid in the reorganization, filings by the CNJ to discontinue certain lines, job protection agreements, and reports of the task force.
- Judicial. Central Railroad Co. of New Jersey Reorganization: U.S.D.C. New Jersey No. B-401-67 [folder 2 of 2], 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1b)
- Judicial. Jacksonville Terminal (Civil Rights), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  Proceeding before the Fifth Circuit Court of Appeals.
- RLEA. RLEA - General, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- RLEA. Constitution and By-Laws, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Pamphlet of the RLEA's By-Laws
- RLEA. American Train Dispatchers' Association, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- RLEA. Brotherhood Railway Carmen of the U.S. and Canada, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- RLEA. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- RLEA. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- RLEA. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers and Blacksmiths, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- RLEA. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- RLEA. International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots of America, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- RLEA. Railway Employes' Department, AFL-CIO, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  Correspondence and Agreement.
- RLEA. Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- RLEA. RLEA Meetings - General, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- RLEA. Miami Meeting of RLEA, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  Includes planning documents, hotel brochures, and minutes of meetings.
- RLEA. Agendas, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  For monthly meetings
- RLEA. Reports of Counsel, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- RLEA. Assessments, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- RLEA. Wages and Rules - General, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- RLEA. Radio-Telephone Equipment Communications, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- RLEA. Employment and Medical Examination, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  Reports of the Committee on Railroad Employee Qualification
- RLEA. 1969 Wage-Rules Movement, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  Agreement between BRAC and U.S. carriers.
- RLEA. 1970 Wage-Rules Movement, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  Agreement between BRS and U.S. carriers, between Shop Crafts and U.S. carriers, between ATDA and U.S. carriers, between RUA and U.S. carriers, and between UTU and U.S. carriers.
- RLEA. Health and Welfare [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 23, Folder 27a)
  Includes information on the 1971 Health and Welfare Movement of railroad labor unions. Also includes information on Travelers Insurance group policies.
- RLEA. Health and Welfare [folder 2 of 2], 1971 (Box 23, Folder 27b)
- RLEA. Travelers' Insurance Company, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- RLEA. Union Shop, General, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- RLEA. Railway Labor Building, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  Financial report.
- RLEA. Committees - General, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- RLEA. Safety Committee, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- RLEA. Executive Committee, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- RLEA. Committee to Study Railroad Mergers, Consolidation etc., 1971 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  Also called Committee on National Transportation Policy.
- RLEA. Committee to Meet with Association of American Railroads, Railroad Labor-Management Relations, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- RLEA. Political Education Committee, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- RLEA. Committee on Railway Labor Act, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- RLEA. Passes, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  In re passes that may or may not be issued by Amtrak.
- RLEA. Prospective Employees - General, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- RLEA. Financial, General, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- RLEA. Financial Statements, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- RLEA. Postage Meter, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- RLEA. Lawyers, General, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- RLEA. Lawyers' Bills, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  Itemized by legal matter.
- RLEA. Strikes, General, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  Includes newspaper clippings
- RLEA. Florida East Coast Railway Strike, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  Includes information on benefits for members on strike (fund GA-23000)
- RLEA. Signalmen's Strike, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  Purchase of Chicago North Western Railway by its employees.
- Railroads. Railroads - General, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Railroads. Railroad Ownership, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Railroads. Association of American Railroads, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Railroads. ASTRO, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Railroads. National Railway Labor Conference, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Railroads. Hospital Associations - General, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Railroads. Southern Pacific Hospital Department, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Railroads. Western Pacific Hospital Association, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, Legislative Council, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO - General [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 24, Folder 22a)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO - General [folder 2 of 2], 1971 (Box 24, Folder 22b)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, Civil Rights, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO Legislative Action Bulletin, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, Executive Council, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Other Organizations. Miscellaneous Organizations - General, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Other Organizations. Transportation Research Forum, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Other Organizations. Charities - General, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Other Organizations. Labor Newspaper, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  Financial reports and By-Laws.
- Other Organizations. NARP, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- International Affairs. International Affairs - General, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  Souvenir book from India's Western Railway Employees' Union, " Golden Jubilee, 1920- 1970.L
- International Affairs. Office of International Labor Affairs - ILAB, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- International Affairs. Team Managers, Office of International Labor Affairs, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Commuter Problems. General, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Commuter Problems. Passenger Service Investigation, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Commuter Problems. Commuter Problems - Philadelphia Service Improvement Corp., 1971 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Commuter Problems. New Haven Problems Including NY Area (Long Island) (Staten Island), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Commuter Problems. Bay Area Rapid Transit (BART), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  Includes reports on arbitrations between BART and various railroad unions.
- Commuter Problems. Adequacies, General, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Commuter Problems. Commuter Service Improvements - HUD - Mass Transit Grants, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  Correspondence in re Delaware River Port Authority application for mass transit grant.
- Commuter Problems. Section 13(c) Agreement - Chicago [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 25, Folder 6a)
  Agreements between West Suburban Mass Transit District and railroad labor unions.
- Commuter Problems. Section 13(c) Agreement - Chicago [folder 2 of 2], 1971 (Box 25, Folder 6b)
  West Suburban Mass Transit District application for a mass transit grant.
- Commuter Problems. Southern Pennsylvania Transportation Project: Hatboro - Warminster, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Commuter Problems. Lake Porter County - Crown Point, Indiana (UMTA), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  Includes employee protection agreements.
- Government. Executive Branch, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Government. House and Senate, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Government. Congressional Campaign Contribution Request, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Government. Appointment of Federal Judgeships, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Government. State Department, General, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Government. Defense Department, General, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Government. Department of Transportation, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Government. DOT, Staff Appointments, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 16)